<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<update xmlns="http://ns.adobe.com/air/framework/update/description/1.0">
  <version>4.7.4.3</version>
  <url>http://www.socialtext.com/desktop/SocialtextDesktop-4.7.4.3.air</url>
  <description><![CDATA[[4.7.4.3 - Sat Aug  6 00:01:05 PDT 2011]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Deleting a signal now refreshes the display immediately.
* Signals: Like/Unlike from other users now displays immediately.

[4.7.4.0 - Sun Jul 24 00:17:38 PDT 2011]
(Features)
* Signals: Support for "Like a Signal" for ST server version 4.7.4+.

(Enhancements)
* Signals: Adopted new layout for threaded view.

[4.7.3.0 - Fri Jun 10 09:18:23 PDT 2011]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Clicking the "Search" sub-tab now sets focus on the search field.
* Signals: Flashback now correctly retrieves "before" and "after" signals again. {bz: 5255}

[4.7.2.0 - Sun May  8 02:56:08 PDT 2011]
(Enhancements)
* Improved OpenSocial Widgets rendering for ST server version 4.7.2+.

[4.7.0.4 - Wed Mar 23 22:55:49 PDT 2011]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Posted signals show up much faster than before.
* Signals: Expanding thread replies is now much faster than before.
* Signals: Disable network toggling when fetching "More" in threadview. {bz: 4979}
* Activity: Resume requests after server upgrade. {bz: 4834}
* Redirect to https:// when connecting to ssl-only appliances with http://. {bz: 5071}
* Compatibility with Adobe AIR 2.6 runtime.

[4.6.3 - Thu Feb 17 14:42:55 PST 2011]
(Features)
* OpenSocial Widgets in pages now work in mini-browser and preview pane. {bz: 4933}
* Syntax-highlighted code blocks now work in mini-browser and preview pane. {bz: 4933}

(Enhancements)
* Fix "DM with mention of same user is displayed as a mention". {bz: 4942}
* Fix "Add a video to a signal, but delete the video Title. Save. See 'null'". {bz: 4942}
* Fix "No video thumbnails in Signal listviews". {bz: 4942}
* Fix "PostTo dropdown menu frozen". {bz: 4976}
* Fix "Toggling 'Show Signals within' results in inconsistent signals display". {bz: 4979}

[4.6.0 - Mon Feb 14 10:52:21 PST 2011]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Fix glitch in displaying embedded video on Windows platforms.
* Signals: Various performance improvements.

[4.5.4.2 - Fri Feb  4 22:06:26 PST 2011]
(Features)
* Signals: Add an "insert video" icon for ST 4.5.4+.
* People: Display emails in people's Colleagues sub-tab.
* People: Added image smoothing and rounded corners for group icons and avatar icons.
* People: Add a per-person Signals sub-tab to agree with Mobile UI.
* People: Display friendly name in the Colleagues sub-tab after following a person.
* Activities: Link "x times ago" in signals events to their permalinks.
* Activities: Display a helpful message if there are no events to display.

(Enhancements)
* Signals: Upgraded to latest Activity Widget codebase for performance improvements.
* Signals: Fix tab/shift-tab navigation for insert web/wiki link panels. {bz: 4299}
* Improve idle-time CPU usage, down from 5%~10% to 1~4%.

[4.5.3 - Tue Jan  4 10:07:43 PST 2011]
(Enhancements)
* Refresh the initial Activity tab if the user switch to it with hotkey (C-2).

[4.5.2.4 - Fri Dec 10 21:15:34 PST 2010]
(Features)
* Activities: Sub-tabs start loading when first switched to them to improve overall performance.
* Signals: Sub-tabs start loading when first switched to them to improve overall performance.
* Signals: Sub-tabs are now populated with backlogged entries upon initial loading.
* Workspace: A new per-page "Tags" sub-tab for displaying, adding and deleting tags.

[4.5.2.2 - Thu Nov 11 17:54:23 PST 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Typing in thread-reply window is now faster. {bz: 4563}
* Signals: Entries in Name and Tag lookaheads now shows up consistently. {bz: 4649}
* Signals: Clicking "More" in per-group threadview no longer results in large time gaps. {bz: 4590}
* Signals: The "X New" notice now goes away after posting a reply. {bz: 4530}
* Signals: Correctly resume push client after a server upgrade. {bz: 4556}
* Signals: On refreshing threaded Signals view, check for deletion of visible entries only.
* Signals: Fix the push client to avoid unnecessary periodic resynchronization. {bz: 4548}

[4.5.1.2 - Fri Oct 22 03:44:14 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Repeated searches in Signal/Search tab now works again. (broken in 4.5.1).
* Signals: Only refresh when push is actually desynchronized.
* Workspaces: "System User" no longer shows a broken avatar. {bz: 4473}
* Login: "Log me in automatically" now works more consistently.

[4.5.1.1 - Wed Oct 20 16:11:10 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Bubbling-up after posting a reply now works again for ST 4.5.0.8+. {bz: 4530}
* Performance: Fetch /data/signals with a reasonable ?after limit when re-synchronizing from push failure.
* Performance: Switching to "All My Groups" for the first time is now much faster. {bz: 4432}

[4.5.1 - Fri Oct  1 02:05:31 PDT 2010]
(Features)
* Auto-renew the time-limited login cookie every 24 hours for server version 4.5.0+.

[4.4.0 - Wed Sep 29 03:00:18 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: When a signal is deleted, remove it from all sub-tabs and popup windows as well.
* Performance: Fetch /data/people only once, not twice, during startup.

[4.3.3 - Wed Sep  8 00:17:57 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Reduced lagging when typing in mention, private, tag and page-name lookaheads.
* Signals: Faster switching of "Post to" when "Show Signals within" is set to "All Groups".
* Signals: Allow reply boxes with only whitespaces in them to close when the focus changes.
* When Encrypted Store fail on Linux, navigate to the Adobe knowledge base with help instructions.

[4.3.2 - Mon Aug 16 01:48:39 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Display tooltips on "Reply to conversation" icons. {bz: 4201}
* Signals: When push is enabled, sending a new signal will still trigger an immediate refresh.
* Workspaces: File in directories with spaces are now uploadable for Mac/AIR2. {bz: 4142}
* Passwords are now saved in the system encrypted store.

[4.3.1 - Wed Aug  4 20:10:48 PDT 2010]
(Features)
* Signals: Support for real-time "Push" delivery mechanism.
* Signals: Add support for actions in signal annotations.
* Signals: Pressing @ now triggers the "mention" autocompleter.
* Signals: Pressing # now triggers the "tag" autocompleter.
* Signals: Show the "Post to" dropdown even if there's only one network to post to.
* Signals: When new signals arrive when the reply box is still open, show a "X new" alert.
* People: Paged people display and people search for ST 4.3.1+.
* People: Show a restricted view when navigating to a restricted profile.
* Workspaces: Fixes locking up when searching for a common word.

(Enhancements)
* {bz: 4201}: Pressing Enter multiple times when sending reply causes duplicated replies.
* {bz: 4098}: Find now works again on Activity subtabs.
* {bz: 4049}: In Add Web Link, "text" field should be above "destination".
* {bz: 4072}: In Add Web Link, supply "http://" prefix and disallow invalid URLs.
* {bz: 4061}: Attach file jump scrolls to top of widget.
* Switching from a single group to "Show All Groups" now retains old signals.

[4.2.1 - Sat Jun 26 09:43:09 PDT 2010]
(Features)
* Signals: New button for uploading attachments.
* Signals: New buttons for inserting tags, web links and wiki links.
* Signals: New "Attachment" subtab listing signals with attachments.
* Signals: Support for displaying attachment and inline thumbnails.
* Signals: Dynamically adjust input box's height for multiline signals.

(Enhancements)
* Signals: Replaced "Followed" and "Mine" subtabs's text with icons.

[4.2.0 - Mon May 31 05:06:30 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Signals: Apply account skin coloring for list-views correctly.
* Signals: Clicking "More" button in threadview now synchronizes with listview.
* Signals: The Search subtab no longer displays a non-functional "More" button.
* Workspaces: Clicking the "Searching..." spinner stops the current search.
* Shorten file names of on-disk config settings to be <256 characters.

[4.1.0.2 - Wed May 26 03:39:02 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Fix a bug in 4.1.0.1 causing the "People" tab to be empty.

[4.1.0.1 - Tue May 11 00:43:21 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Fix a bug where incoming signals sometimes freeze Desktop when typing a reply.
* Increased height of Input area for Signals and Conversation boxes.

[4.1.0 - Thu May  6 18:22:01 PDT 2010]
(Features)
* Signals: Support for thread view of Signal Conversations by default.
* Signals: Click "x ago" to open Permalink in browser.
* Signals: New navigation hot keys: C-8 (Previous subtab), C-9 (Next subtab).
* Signals: New view-toggling hot key: C-0 (Toggles between list/thread views)
* Signals: Click "as a topic/reply" to launch Conversation view.
* Signals: Fetch 100 signals on startup by default (was 50).
* People: Hide deactivated/deleted users from @-completion and directory.
* UI: Switched to a new icon set, free of the airplane sigil.

(Enhancements)
* Signals: Improved interactivity when displaying large batch of signals.
* Conversation: Clicking a signal entry to focus on the reply input box.
* People: Logout then login into another server now properly refreshes the list.

[4.0.2 - Thu Apr  8 19:59:23 PDT 2010]
(Enhancements)
* "Log me in automatically" now takes effect upon the first try.

[4.0.1 - Thu Mar 25 08:15:27 PDT 2010]
(Features)
* Users can now directly install, upgrade and launch Desktop from an appliance.
* Administrators can now turn off auto-updating from system console.
* Support Authenticating Proxies in Mac OS X's System Settings.
* Signals: Support for server-configurable expanded input limits.
* Signals: Increased default input limits from 140 to 400.

(Enhancements)
* Signals: Add a ":" separator between User and timestamp for improved legibility.
* Signals: On Login, reset "Signal To" to Primary group if it was set to "All Groups".
* Signals: Reliably resume updates when internet connection was stopped and resumed.
* People: Logout/Login no longer results in duplicated people entries.
* People: Sort names alphabetically for the "All My Groups" list.
* People: Hide Refresh button when People list is still refreshing.
* Workspaces: Inter-workspace links now correctly opens in lightbox view.

[4.0.0 - Fri Feb 26 15:26:02 PST 2010]
(Features)
* Signals: @-completion now displays only members in the "Signal to" network.
* People: New "Open" button in a Profile to navigate to its Web interface.
* Activities: Support for "...More...", with much faster refresh speed.
* Activities: Update style to match the Dashboard widget.
* Activities: Renamed the tab from "Activity" to "Activities".
* Activities: Include People events in display, in addition to Page events.
* Activities: Include "Follow" events in display.
* Status Bar: Click to display version history.
* Status Bar: Show the logged-in user name.
* Login: Add a link to follow us on Twitter and Facebook.

(Enhancements)
* Signals: Say "Show Signals within" instead of "Show Signals from".
* People: Filter text no longer affects @-completion in Signals and "Edited By" in Workspaces.
* People: Much improved performance; no longer freezes up upon first login.
* Correctly restore the Active Tab and Subtabs upon restart.
* Server timeout set to 60 seconds for improved performance.
* Gracefully delay requests when server response is slower than update interval.
* Add version number to user-agent string for easier server log analysis.

[3.7.5 - Mon Feb  1 15:54:18 PST 2010]
(Enhancements)
* Fix {bz: 3504}: Hidden profile fields should stay hidden in People's Profiles.
* Fix {bz: 3528}: Workspace/Network lists are now remembered by ID, not by index.

[3.7.4 - Fri Jan 15 13:43:23 PST 2010]
(Features)
* Settings: New "Display all Personal messages" option to filter popups.
* Signals: Support for Socialtext Groups in "Signal to" and "Show Signals from".
* Signals: When "Signals to" changes, change "Show Signals from" to match.
* Signals: Inform the user when "Show Signals from" changes away from "Signals to".
* Signals: Entries in Followed/Mine/Personal/Sent/Link sub-tabs are now Flashbackable.
* People: Support for Socialtext Groups in All People listing.

(Enhancements)
* Login: No longer display a harmless error message when the server had no signals.
* Signals: "Show Signal from" no longer scrolls horizontally with long Network names.
* Signals: Popups should now consume less CPU when fading in and fading out.
* Signals: Disable the "Signal to" dropdown only when replying, not when mentioning.
* Workspaces: Renamed the tab from "Workspace" for better consistency with Web UI.
* Workspaces: SocialCalc spreadsheets are now displayed using the same Web UI styling.
* Workspaces: Only allow double-clicking on known-displayable attachments.

[3.7.0 - Tue Nov 24 07:07:05 PST 2009]
(Features)
* Signals: Double-click a search result to see its historical context as "Flashback".
* Signals: Support per-network views in addition to "Show Signals from all networks".
* Workspace: Add "All Workspaces" search for server version v3.7.1.2+.
* Workspace: Double-click an image or HTML attachment to view it in a lightbox.

(Enhancements)
* "Minimize" in Microsoft Windows now minimizes to system tray.
* Login: Do not pre-fill Server URL, but offer a button to set to Socialtext Hosted.
* Signals: Disable "Signal to Account" dropdown when replying or direct-messaging.
* Signals: Clicking on the Signal Search view now auto-focuses on search term input box.
* Signals: @-completion now work reliably the first time after login.
* People: Use the ST star icon for "Follow/Stop following this person" instead of a checkbox.
* People: Keyword filtering no longer interferes with Signal tab's @-completion.
* Workspace: Correctly style Wiki text in preview and lightbox.
  (e.g. horizontal borders in tables are now visible.)

[3.6.2 - Mon Sep 28 23:31:04 PDT 2009]
* Add support for Signal Search for Socialtext server v3.6.3+.
* Failed login to www.socialtext.net will now fallback to www1 for Free50 users.

[3.6.1 - Mon Sep 21 10:27:15 PDT 2009]
* Fix the case where filtering for non-existent People deactivates People tab.

[3.6.0 - Sun Sep  6 04:19:03 PDT 2009]
* Fix incorrect People tab display with Socialtext server v3.6.0+.
* Fix the bug where too general a search freezes Workspace tab.

[3.5.9 - Thu Sep  3 21:22:21 PDT 2009]
* Double-clicking a row in Workspace tab now opens the Page inside a mini-browser.
* A page set as home page in the mini-browser will now open immediately after Login.
* Support for Activity tab display with Socialtext server v3.6.0+.

[3.5.8 - Thu Aug 20 16:44:17 PDT 2009]
* Fix a performance issue by checking deletion for visible-in-viewport signals only.

[3.5.7 - Thu Aug 13 20:03:52 PDT 2009]
* Add support for Deleting signals for Socialtext server v3.5.9+.

[3.5.6 - Thu Jul  2 19:56:08 PDT 2009]
* Add support for Activity feed in Socialtext server v3.5.7+.
* Activity feed should no longer be refreshed when already logged out.

[3.5.5 - Thu Jun 18 00:42:44 PDT 2009]
* Hide "Private to" button if the server does not support private message.
* Disable the "Replies and Mentions" tab if the server supports neither.
* Send @UserName, not {user:*}, if the server does not support user mentions.

[3.5.4 - Wed May 27 23:53:13 PDT 2009]
* Names not prefixed with @ will no longer appear in the @ tab.
* Fix the bug where Signals with smiley icons erroneously appearing in the @ tab.

[3.5.3 - Fri May 15 04:59:03 PDT 2009]
* New "Private to" and "Insert mention" buttons for Signals tab.
* New "Refresh" button in the Workspace tab to refresh the workspaces list.
* Clicking the popup notification now stops currently queued popups.
* Ctrl-R now consistently refreshes People and Workspace list in those tabs.
* Drag-and-drop URLs from Browser into the Signals tab now inserts links.
* Drag-and-drop text into the Signals tab now correctly appends the text.
* Rename Signals and Activity's "My Colleagues" tab to "Followed".
* Upon logout, SD now clears all leftover data from the previous session.
* Auto-correct typed "(@UserName)" to "( @UserName )" to form a proper mention.
* Private Signals that mentions you again now appears in @ tab as well.
* Fix the bug that sometimes turns the People/Profile tab blank.
* Add Server URL to the default status bar.

[3.5.2 - Fri May  1 15:43:45 PDT 2009]
* Support for proper replies, private messages, and user mentions.
* New "Private message" sub-tab for Signals to list private messages.
* New "...more..." button at the bottom of Signals/All to fetch older Signals.
* New "Save as..." button to save Signals as HTML file on disk.
* New "Help" button on the top bar, next to "Settings".
* New "I don't know my password" link on login panel.
* Typing "@" in the Signal text body now pulls down people's photos.
* Typing "@" in the Signal text body now offers "private message" buttons.
* "Replies"/"Private"/"Links" are now icon tabs, not text tabs.
* On Workspace selection change, redo search unless one is in progress.
* Mac: New "Reset application window" item in dock icon's right-click menu.

[3.5.1 - Sat Apr 11 03:04:41 PDT 2009]
* If the server supports invitation, display an invite link.
* If the server supports skinning, skin the client accordingly upon login.
* Show "Welcome, New User!" link when the user had not set first/last name yet.
* Show "Upload your photo!" link when the user had not uploaded their photo yet.
* Added a "refresh" button to the Activity tab and the People tab.
* Changed "Hide signals from other networks" to "Show signals from other networks".
* When login is successful, immediately re-run the previous Workspace query.
* For Outlook compatibility, we no longer show First/Last names when clicking email links.

[3.5.0 - Tue Mar 24 20:06:54 PDT 2009]
* The default server URL was incorrectly set to www2.socialtext.net;
  it should be www.socialtext.net.

[3.4.2 - Sat Mar 21 06:54:56 PDT 2009]
* Users can choose which network to Signal to.
* Signals show which network the Signal was sent to.
* Typing "@" in Signals input box now auto-completes user names.
* New "People" tab showing a people directory.
* Users can view profile information on individual users.
* New "Workspace" tab for searching on individual workspaces.
* Drag-and-drop uploading and downloading Page attachments.
* In Signals tab, new "@Replies" tab collects signals mentioning your name.
* In Signals tab, new "Links" tab collects signals containing hyperlinks.

[3.4.0 - Thu Feb 26 17:37:29 PST 2009]
* First public release.
]]></description>
</update>
